Seen, I'm Logy Chronicle!
Today I'd like to answer a few questions to help you get to know us a little better.
I would like to answer your questions!
We will answer one by one in a row!
Let's get started!
Let's start the questions!
Name!
Name! I am Hashida Honaka!
I am Hiroha Yoshida!
I am Karin Onoda!
I am Ayana Muraguchi!
I am Hasumi Kamimura!
I am Yuriya Matsumaru!
I am Hana Shimakawa
I am Rena Akamimura
I am Sonoem
My birthday is October 17
July 8
January 23rd
February 11
February 25th
February 26.
April 18.
June 15.
February 4.
Height 151cm
Maybe 155cm
156 cm
Sixteen-one-four-five.
What?
Private.
Describe your personality in one word
Princess
Positive thinking
Hate to lose
Energetic
An idiot!
Simple and kind!
Wow!
I'm Shibono!
Heartwarming!
Funny!
My dream Hello Project member is Ruru Danbara of JuiceJuice!
I am Mizuki Fukumura!
I am Yuka Miyazaki!
They are Mariaki Makino of Morning Musume。24 and Ryumoe Kamikuro of Androom!
It's Ayumi Ishida from Morning Musume。 24!
It is Mao Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory!
Love!
This is Ms. Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 They are Mizuki Fukumura and Masaki Sato, who graduated from Morning Musume。
It's Ms. Reirou Ise from Angeleum!
It's Rio Kitagawa from Morning Musume 24 and Ruri Matsubara from Rosy Chronicle!
Octopus or squid? I'm a squid person!
Octopus! Both! Octopus! Octopus! Squid!
Squid!
My favorite fishery...
Culture is Japanese, Calligraphy...
Numeracy and Physical Education
Biology Integrated and Physical Education
Arts and Crafts Art
Modern Japanese language and language culture.
Japanese Language
Music, Home Economics and Physical Education
My favorite food is
Yakitori
Pasta, apples
Ramen Sushi
Fried rice. I only buy it for money.
Strawberry Daifuku and ramen
Sushi and fruits.
Hand-rolled sushi, hamburgers and sweets
If I were to compare myself to an animal
I'm lazy.
Maybe a squirrel
Black.
Lazy
Koala
Cat.
Squirrel.
Hamster.
My hobby is watching baseball games
My hobby is watching jellyfish
My hobby is
Hamster.
My hobby is watching soccer.
My hobby is bowling
Drinking milk and dancing
Playing with my sister and drawing pictures
Watching idols.
Watching anime and movies.
I go to karaoke and dance.
My favorite sport is baseball.
Karate, Aikido and Basketball.
Swimming
Badminton and baseball.
Dancing and marathon running
I watch idols.
Billiards, table soccer and table tennis.
Roller-skating, if I may say so.
Badminton.
Baseball, swimming and running.
My favorite four-letter word is "single-mindedness.
Single-minded focus
First, advanced
Do what you say you're going to do
Execution of a word
Sanzaki Nicho
seven days in a year, eight days in a week
one year, one day, one year, one day
One life, one meeting
The source of my energy is watching baseball games
The source of my energy is my family
Oronamin C
Sleeping
Milk
My sister who is 10 years younger than me
Music
Laughing
My favorite Hello Project song is
Morning Musume。' 14's
Toki wo Koete Sora wo Koete (Beyond Time and Beyond the Sky) by Morning Musume。
Juice Juice's
I can live on my own, that's a compliment.
That's a compliment.
It's "Wonderful World" by Juice Juice!
Morning Musume。 18's
It's in the middle of Y0!
Morning Musume。 21's What's wrong with love
Morning Musume。 21's Teenage Solution
Morning Musume。' 14's Smiling Strange Sun!
I'm sorry even though I know by Country Girls
Morning Musume。 24's Strongest!
The only thing about Rosy Chronicle's members that I think is unbeatable.
Their hair and makeup!
Their athleticism.
The weight of their luggage.
Genki's bowling score
Milk love and dancing
Makeup.
Voice.
Maybe dexterity
Definitely not nervous
If I could take only one thing to a deserted island, it would definitely be sunscreen.
No, definitely a knife.
I'm fine.
Definitely a digital camera, definitely a cell phone, definitely a milk cow.
Definitely a water machine.
Definitely a place to sleep
Definitely water
Definitely Doraemon
That's awesome!
If you could switch places among the members of the Rosy Chronicles, who would it be?
Yuriya Matsubara.
I would be Hana Shimakawa
Honoka Hashida
I'd like to switch with Yoshin Onoda
Koshi for the eyes
Ayana
Soumaime
I'm Yoshikazu Onoda
I am Honoka Hashida
Finally, a word to the viewers watching the video
I love you so much, and I hope you will continue to support me.
I'll do my best to cheer you all up!
I'm not Karin, I'm Karin.
How are you all doing?
Thank you for your support from now on.
I'll drink milk and do my best.
Thank you for your support.
I'm Pistachio.
I'll do my best, so please support me!
Please keep supporting me, I love you!
I'll do my best for the rest of my life
I'll do my best from now on, so please support me!
That's all.
I'm done.
So that's it.
So, we answered a lot of questions, but did you get to know us?
Did you get to know us?
Did you know us?
Thank you very much. Please continue to support Rosy Chronicle.
That's all for now, Rosy Chronicle.